https://www.verizon.com/about/privacy/do-not-sell-my-info

Privacy Policy Summary
Current:
Do not sell my information
EnglishEspañol
We recommend that you view our Privacy Policy online or on your mobile device for a better design and navigation experience and the ability to seamlessly access links and other documents. This version is provided so that you can print a version of our full Privacy Policy in a single document.
Your choices
The California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA) gives California consumers the right to say no to the sale of personal information. The term “sale” is broadly defined by the CCPA and includes sharing personal information for monetary or other valuable consideration, but does not cover all sharing of personal information.
We do not sell information that personally identifies our customers or other consumers such as name, telephone number or email address. We may share that type of information with directory publishers and for caller ID purposes, and as otherwise described in our Privacy Policy.
We also allow Verizon Media and third-party advertising companies to collect information about your activity on our websites and in our apps, for example through cookies and similar technologies, mobile ad identifiers, pixels, web beacons and social network plugins. These ad entities use information they collect to help us provide more relevant Verizon advertisements and other advertising purposes.  This activity may be considered a sale under the CCPA.
This page gives you information about your choices regarding cookies and other technology, as well as additional privacy choices offered by Verizon. For more details about the information Verizon collects, how that information is used and shared, and your choices, please visit our Privacy Policy.
Open all
Close all
Digital advertising
You have choices about whether certain information collected on websites and through mobile applications, including Verizon’s, is used to customize advertising.
Digital advertising choices
Visit the Digital Advertising Alliance's Consumer Choices page to learn more about how you can limit the collection of information. App users can opt out by using your device settings to “Limit Ad Tracking” (for iOS devices) or “Opt out of Ads Personalization” (on Android devices).
Advertising, insights and verification services
You have choices about participating in advertising, insights and verification services.
Advertising and insights programs
Mobile customers
Verizon Wireless customers can view and change preferences regarding participation in Verizon Selects in the Verizon Selects Preference Center.
Verizon Wireless customers can view and change preferences regarding participation in the Relevant Mobile Advertising program and the Business & Marketing Insights program on the privacy choices page in My Verizon or by calling 866-211-0874.
Verizon Wireless customers who do not want information shared with third parties for purposes of verification can opt out by visiting the privacy choices page in My Verizon.
Home customers
Fios TV customers can view and change preferences regarding participation in Verizon’s Relevant TV Advertising program in My Verizon.
View and Change Preferences Regarding Participation In Verizon’s Relevant TV Advertising Program
Relevant TV Advertising
To opt out of participating in Relevant TV advertising:
- Go to the Services area of My Verizon
- Click on TV
- Select the Manage TV Advertising Preferences link within My TV Service
You will need your user ID and password to access your online account.
Fios Internet customers can view and change preferences regarding participation in Verizon’s Relevant Online Advertising program in My Verizon.
View and Change Preferences Regarding Participation In Verizon’s Relevant Online Advertising Program
To opt out of participating in the Relevant Online Advertising program:
- Go to the Services area of My Verizon
- Click on Internet
- Select the Manage Online Advertising Preferences link within My Internet Service
You will need your user ID and password to access your online account.
Marketing and communication
You have choices about marketing and communication.
The Verizon family of companies
You have choices about whether Customer Proprietary Network Information and certain credit information may be used and shared within Verizon for specific marketing purposes.
Customer Proprietary Network Information
Customer Proprietary Network Information (or CPNI) is information that relates to the type, quantity, destination, technical configuration, location, amount of use and related billing information of your telecommunications or interconnected Voice over Internet Protocol (VoIP) services. Federal law governs our use and sharing of CPNI.
Mobile customers
Verizon Wireless customers may limit the use and sharing of Customer Proprietary Network Information within Verizon for marketing services that are different from the ones you have by calling 800-333-9956 or visiting the privacy choices page in My Verizon.
Home customers
Fios customers may limit the use and sharing of Customer Proprietary Network Information within Verizon for marketing services that are different from the ones you have by calling 866-483-9700.
Fios customers may limit the sharing of credit information within Verizon for the marketing of new products and services by calling 844-366-2879.
Marketing
You can limit the ways we may send marketing to you.
Telemarketing: Opt out of marketing-related calls by calling 800-VERIZON. It can take up to 30 days to remove you from existing marketing campaigns.
Emails: Opt out of receiving marketing-related emails by following the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of marketing emails you receive.
Text messages: Opt out of receiving marketing-related texts by following the unsubscribe instructions included in the texts you receive.
Postal mail: Opt out of receiving marketing-related mail by calling 800-VERIZON. Note that even if you unsubscribe, you could still receive mail when we use a bulk mailing service that delivers to all homes within a zip code.
Door-to-door marketing: Opt out of door-to-door marketing by calling 800-VERIZON.
Other choices
You have other choices available to you.
Mobile location analytics
Verizon Business Group provides mobile location analytics reporting services to business customers. This service helps businesses understand their customers, such as how they are moving around their stores. The services collect and de-identify device identifiers from cell devices that come in contact with our business customers’ Wi-Fi network equipment. You can learn more about the service and how to opt out in the Mobile Location Analytics Privacy Notice.
Device and router location
The operating system on your mobile device collects device location information and shares it with apps you have permitted to have this information, including some Verizon apps. You can toggle the setting to “off” using the settings menu on your device. You can also use the settings menu to toggle location information to “off” for specific apps, but you may need to enable it for navigation or other location features to work in those apps. You can rename your router to include “_nomap” or “_optout” if you don’t want us to use the location of your Wi-Fi router access point to improve the accuracy of our services or apps. For example, change “Myrouter” to “Myrouter_nomap”.
Nielsen measurement
The Fios TV app and website include Nielsen software that collects information for market research purposes. Fios TV app users can opt out by using your device settings to “Limit Ad Tracking” (for iOS devices) or “Opt out of Ads Personalization” (on Android devices). Fios TV website users can view and change preferences regarding participation in your Fios TV account Settings.
Accessibility Resource Center
Skip to main content
Services & Solutions
Home Services
Mobile Plans
Small and Medium Business
Enterprise Solutions
Verizon Connect
Multi Edge Compute (MEC)
Aol.
